[
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "Name the administrator of Cloud City who appears in The Empire Strikes Back?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Lando Calrissian ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chewbacca",
        "Han Solo",
        "Senador Bail Organa"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "Who plays Luke Skywalker throughout the series?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Mark Hamill",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Will Smith",
        "Leonardo DiCaprio",
        "Tom Cruise"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "Which character, in Return of the Jedi says “it’s a trap!”?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Admiral Ackbar",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Luke Skywalker",
        "Greedo",
        "Biggs Darklighter"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "What year did the first Star Wars film come out?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "1977",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2004",
        "1989",
        "1944"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "Which planet is Jar Jar Binks from?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Naboo",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tatooine",
        "Coruscant",
        "Alderaan"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "10. Ewan Macgregor and Alec Guinness play which character?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Owen Lars",
        "C-3PO",
        "Anakin Skywalker"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "In Blade Runner, the artificial humans are formally called what?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Replicant",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Recombinant",
        "Synthezoid",
        "Android"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "Who directed Blade Runner, in addition to the sci-fi classic Alien?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Ridley Scott",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Steven Spielberg",
        "George Lucas",
        "M. Night Shyamalan"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "In Interestellar, what natural disaster is happening on Earth, that will eventually cause the human race to go extinct?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "Dust Storms",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Earthquakes",
        "Volcanoes",
        "Hurricanes"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "In Interestellar, What does the message from the ghost say in Murphy's room.",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "correct_answer": "STAY",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "I Love You",
        "Go to Miller's Planet",
        "Leave Now"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "question": "In Interestellar, why does Dr. Mann lie about his planet?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "He wants to live - survival instinct!",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "He wants his planet to the be the one humans live on.",
        "He believes there are 2 planets humans can live on.",
        "He doesn't lie."

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "12",
      "question": "In Matrix, What exactly did taking the red pill mean?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "The red pill allows us to free ourselves from the virtual reality of the Matrix and lead us to the real world",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The red pill allows you to forget everything that happened and stay in the virtual reality of the Matrix",
        "The red pill allows you to jump to another dimension",
        "The red pill allows you to remember the past and foresee the future"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "13",
      "question": "In Matrix, to find Trinity, Neo must follow...",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "A white rabbit, just like in Alice in Wonderland",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A white snake",
        "A white owl",
        "A white pigeon"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "14",
      "question": "In Matrix, what was the job of Thomas Anderson (Neo) before starting his particular adventure?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "Programmer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Computer technical service",
        "Hardware designer",
        "professional gamer"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "15",
      "question": "In 2001: A Space Odyssey, What airline's name appeared on the spacecraft that Dr. Heywood Floyd took to get to the space station?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "Pan Am",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ryanair",
        "AmericanAirlines",
        "easyJet"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "16",
      "question": "In Back to the future, which type of car is converted into a time machine?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "DeLorean",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dodge",
        "Mitsubishi",
        "Ferrari"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "17",
      "question": "Who directed Back to the Future?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "Robert Zemeckis",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Steven Spielberg",
        "George Lucas",
        "Ron Howard"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "18",
      "question": "In Back to the future, what speed did the DeLorean need to hit to be able to time travel?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "88mph / 141kmh",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "73mph / 117 kmh",
        "76mph / 122 kmh",
        "80mph / 128 kmh"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "19",
      "question": "In Inception, why is Cobb wanted by the police?",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "He murdered his wife",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "He robbed a big company",
        "He is a serial killer",
        "He sneaks into other's dreams"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "20",
      "question": "In Arrival (2016), the aliens are called...",
      "category": "science fiction",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "correct_answer": "Heptapods",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Angosian",
        "Talaxian",
        "Xindi"

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "21",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "question": "This movie contains the quote, &quot;I love the smell of napalm in the morning!&quot;",
      "correct_answer": "Apocalypse Now",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Platoon",
        "The Deer Hunter",
        "Full Metal Jacket"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "22",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "question": "In the 1999 movie Fight Club, which of these is not a rule of the &quot;fight club&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Always wear a shirt",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "You do not talk about FIGHT CLUB",
        "Only two guys to a fight",
        "Fights will go on as long as they have to"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "23",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "question": "What was the first James Bond film?",
      "correct_answer": "Dr. No",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Goldfinger",
        "From Russia With Love",
        "Thunderball"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "24",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "question": "Which actors made up the trio in &quot;The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly&quot;? ",
      "correct_answer": "Clint Eastwood, Eli Wallach, and Lee Van Cleef",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sergio Leone, Ennio Morricone, and Tonino Delli Colli",
        "Yul Brynner, Steve McQueen, and Charles Bronson",
        "Aldo Giuffr&egrave;, Mario Brega, and Luigi Pistilli"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "25",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "question": "Which movie contains the quote, &quot;Say hello to my little friend!&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Scarface",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reservoir Dogs",
        "Heat",
        "Goodfellas"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "26",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "question": "Leonardo Di Caprio won his first Best Actor Oscar for his performance in which film?",
      "correct_answer": "The Revenant",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Wolf Of Wall Street",
        "Shutter Island",
        "Inception"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "27",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "question": "Who plays &quot;Bruce Wayne&quot; in the 2008 movie &quot;The Dark Knight&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Christian Bale",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Michael Caine",
        "Ron Dean",
        "Heath Ledger"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "28",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "2",
      "question": "In Mad Max Fury Road, How did War Boy, Nux, refer to Max?",
      "correct_answer": "Blood Bag",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Slave",
        "Body Bag",
        "Meat"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "29",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "question": "How many infinity stones are in MCU?",
      "correct_answer": "6",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5",
        "7",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "30",
      "category": "action",
      "difficulty": "1",
      "question": "What type of doctor is Doctor Strange?",
      "correct_answer": "A neurosurgeon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A Endocrinologist",
        "A Nephrologist",
        "A Oncologist"
      ]
    }
  ]
